Guide to the Vassar College Faculty Minutes, 1865-2018
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Vassar College Faculty Minutes
1865-2018
Vassar College
10 cubic feet (21 volumes and 12 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Minutes from faculty meetings and some faculty committee meetings, 1865-2018. Includes an index for the years 1865-1924.
Scope and Content Note
Minutes from faculty meetings and some faculty committee meetings, 1865-2018. Includes an index for the years 1865-1924.
Access
This collection is restricted. Contact the staff for additional information.
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Faculty
Subjects:
Women's colleges--New York (State)--Poughkeepsie
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Committees and Boards
Encoding Information
Encoded by Elizabeth Clarke, April 2007. Updated by Emma Gronbeck, January 2024.
Acquisition Information
Minutes dating from 1967-1989 transferred from the Vassar College Office of the Registrar in July 2007 [A2007-045]. Earlier minutes transferred from the same office an earlier unknown year.
Minutes dating from 1990-2018 transferred from the Registrar in March 2023 [A2023-012].
Container List
- Faculty Minutes
  - 1865 Sep - 1880 Jun (Volume 1)
  - 1880 Sep - 1894 May (Volume 2)
  - 1894 Sep - 1900 May (Volume 3)
  - 1900 Sep - 1907 Jun (Volume 4)
  - 1907 Sep - 1915 May (Volume 5)
  - 1915 Feb - 1919 Oct (Volume 6)
  - 1920 Jan - 1924 Feb (Volume 7)
  - 1924 Feb - 1930 May (Volume 8)
  - 1930 Sep - 1938 Feb (Volume 9)
  - 1938 Mar - 1943 Feb (Volume 10)
  - 1943 Mar - 1946 Apr (Volume 11)
  - 1946 Apr - 1949 Oct (Volume 12)
  - 1949 Oct - 1954 Jun (Volume 13)
  - 1954 Sep - 1958 Oct (Volume 14)
  - 1958 Oct - 1962 Apr (Volume 15)
  - 1962 May - 1965 Dec (Volume 16)
  - 1966 Jan - 1967 Jun (Volume 17)
  - 1967 Sep - 1968 Jun (Volume 18)
  - 1957-1958 (Folder 7.01)
  - 1958-1959 (Folder 7.02)
  - 1959-1960 (Folder 7.03)
  - 1960-1961 (Folder 7.04)
  - 1961-1962 (Folder 7.05)
  - 1962-1963 (Folder 7.06)
  - 1963-1964 (Folder 7.07)
  - 1964-1965 (Folder 7.08)
  - 1965-1966 (Folder 7.09)
  - 1966-1967 (Folder 7.10)
  - 1968 Sep - 1969 Oct (Folder 1.01)
  - 1969 Nov - 1970 May (Folder 1.02)
  - 1970 May - 1971 May (Folder 1.03)
  - 1971 Sep - 1972 Dec (Folder 1.04)
  - 1973 Jan - 1974 Dec (Folder 1.05)
  - 1975 Jan - 1977 May (Folder 1.06)
  - 1977 Sep - 1979 Feb (Folder 2.01)
  - 1979 Apr - 1981 Feb (Folder 2.02)
  - 1981 Mar - 1983 Apr (Folder 2.03)
  - 1983 May - 1984 Nov (Folder 2.04)
  - 1984 Dec - 1986 Nov (Folder 2.05)
  - 1986 Dec- 1988 Apr (Folder 3.01)
  - 1988 May - 1989 Mar (Folder 3.02)
  - 1989 Apr - 1990 Dec (Folder 3.03)
  - 1991 Feb - 1992 Oct (Folder 3.04)
  - 1992 Nov - 1994 Apr (Folder 3.05)
  - 1994 May - 1995 Apr (Folder 3.06)
  - 1995 Apr - 1996 Sep (Folder 4.01)
  - 1996 Oct - 1997 Sep (Folder 4.02)
  - 1997 Nov - 1998 Dec (Folder 4.03)
  - 1999 Feb - 2000 Apr (Folder 4.04)
  - 2000 May - 2001 Oct (Folder 4.05)
  - 2001 Dec - 2003 Apr (Folder 4.06)
  - 2003 May - 2004 May (Folder 5.01)
  - 2004 Sep - 2005 Oct (Folder 5.02)
  - 2005 Nov - 2007 Mar (Folder 5.03)
  - 2007 Apr - 2008 Sep (Folder 5.04)
  - 2008 Oct - 2010 Feb (Folder 5.05)
  - 2010 Mar - 2011 Nov (Folder 5.06)
  - 2011 Dec - 2012 Oct (Folder 6.01)
  - 2012 Nov - 2013 Apr (Folder 6.02)
  - 2013 May - 2014 Apr (Folder 6.03)
  - 2014 May - 2015 May (Folder 6.04)
  - 2015 Sep - 2016 Dec (Folder 6.05)
  - 2017 Feb - 2018 May (Folder 6.06)
- Indexes
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 1, 1865-1880 (Folders 8.01-8.03)
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 2, 1880-1894 (Folders 8.04-8.06)
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 3, 1894-1900 (Volume 19)
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 3, 1894-1900 (Folders 8.07-8.09)
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 4, 1900-1907 (Volume 20)
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 4, 1900-1907 (Folders 9.01-9.03)
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 5, 1907-1914 (Volume 21)
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 5, 1907-1914 (Folders 9.04-9.06)
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 6, 1915-1919 (Folders 9.07-9.09)
  - Index to Faculty Minutes, Vol. 7, 1920-1924 (Folders 10.01-10.03)
- Card catalog for Faculty Minutes, undated (Boxes 11-12)